--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调：心仪Sally 潇妹纸
翻译：死神夜月 夏日尾日记 RK翔 千欲 影子
校对：影子  故故好忙
I114号 116号和260号已经就位
We have India 114, 116, and 260 in position.
104号距离目标直线航程还有500码 等待进一步指示
Flight 104 is 500 yards in trail, waiting for your go.
这里 在这儿 就是那艘船
That's it, right there. There's our guy.
开始接近目标
Begin your final approach to the target.
104号直升机飞行员 收到
Pilot on flight 104, copy that.
妈的!
Shit!
Walter 快醒醒 海关的人来了
Walter, wake up. Customs.
什么? 谁来了?
What? Who?
快把背包找给我 钥匙在哪儿?
We need the fucking bag. Where the fuck is the key?
固定好绳索 到另一边做好警备
Tighten that line. Now secure the other side.
慢点 慢点上
Easy, easy up.
好的 没事的
Okay, Okay.
快点 快点把它装进包里
Hurry up. Come on, put it in the bag.
快点!
Come on!
把这个拉上去 快点 快点!
Pull this up. Come on, come on. Let's go!
快走 Andy
Go, Andy.
站住! 我们是联邦警员! 别动!
Stop! Federal officer! Don't move!
禁运品
抱歉 打断一下 各位 大家注意一下好吗?
Excuse me. Excuse me, y'all. Can I have everybody's attention?
我想敬今天的新郎新娘 Danny和Shelly
I want to do a quick toast to the bride and groom, Danny and Shelly.
祝贺你们
Congratulations.
真难以置信 哥们 我竟然结婚了 Chris
I can't believe it, man. I'm fucking married, Chris.
Danny 我知道 我刚才就站在你旁边
Danny, I know. I was standing right there with you.
瞧 再来看看这个混蛋如何?
Look, what about this fucking guy?
他是我最好的朋友 也是我的伴郎
He's my best friend, best man at my wedding.
但他甚至都不记得我婚宴是在哪儿举行的
He doesn't even remember that this is where my reception was.
谢天谢地 他还没喝醉
Thank God, he's sober.
你不记得了吗?
You don't remember?
我记得自己吐到了Kate的鞋子上了
I remember throwing up on Kate's shoes.
是的 我也记得
Yeah, I remember, too.
我很抱歉
I apologized for that.
各位 跟我一起唱
Everybody, do it like this.
我是说 你曾是跟Lennon和McCartney一样出名的走私贩
I mean, you were like the Lennon and McCartney of smuggling.
你是怎么走私那辆法拉利的? 你当时把它藏在哪儿了?
How do you smuggle a fucking Ferrari? Where do you hide it?
我们没藏那辆车
We didn't.
我们让海关在港口扣押了那辆车
We let customs seize it in port.
把你手机给我
Give me your phone.
把汽车部件拿出来
You take the guts out.
变速器 布线系统
The transmission, the wiring system.
把那些全都拿出来 藏在另一个集装箱里
Take all that shit out, hide it inside other containers.
当海关拍卖了那辆车之后
So, when customs auctions off the car,
买主只能买到个法拉利空壳子
he gets himself a Ferrari for next to nothing.
他只买了个空壳子?
He just bought the empty shell?
是的 他在拍卖会上只买了个空壳子
Yes, he got the empty shell at the auction.
然后我们...
And then we...
- 再把缺的那些部分卖给他  - 再把汽车部件卖给他
- Sell him the missing parts.  - Sold him back the guts.
这样他算弄到辆完整的新法拉利
And he's got himself a new Ferrari
远比你花钱买一辆破丰田车便宜
for less than you paid for that piece-of-shit Honda.
丰田车很不错
It's a nice Honda.
是的 那就是你住在丰田车里的原因 对吧?
Yeah, that's why you live in it, right?
因为你那辆破丰田还不错
Because it's a nice fucking Honda.
我可以跟我的妻子跳一支舞吗?
Can I dance with my wife?
嘿 你好吗 哥们?
Hey, what's up, buddy?
如果可以的话 你能再给我拿一罐这个吗?
Can I get another one of these when you get a chance?
嘿 Chris
Hey, Chris.
Church 嘿
Church, hey.
最近过得怎么样 伙计?
How are you doing, man?
好久没见了 你去哪儿了?
Long time, no see. Where you been?
呃 我现在住在Algiers
Well, I'm living out in Algiers now.
你住那儿干什么?
The fuck are you doing out there?
那里很不错 我很喜欢
It's nice, I like it out there.
那里很适合安家
It's good for the family.
像你这样的家伙不应该待在Algiers的 Chris
A guy like you don't belong in Algiers, Chris.
你现在的工作是什么?
What are you doing for work?
我自己开了公司 帮人安装报警系统
I started my own business, setting up alarm systems.
再倒一杯 好吗?
Fill that up, will you?
你老爸进了监狱就把你吓成这样?
Your old man getting jailed freak you out?
可能吧
I guess.
除此之外 我现在还有妻子和两个儿子 懂吗?
That, and having a wife and two little boys, you know?
我知道
Yeah.
尽管这样 你还是应该坚持做你擅长的 Chris
You've got to stick to what you're good at, though, Chris.
听着 我曾经想帮你老爸摆平那个船长
Listen, I offered to take care of that ship captain for your dad.
但他拒绝了
He said no.
不管怎么样 Chris 如果你还想重操旧业的话
Anyway, Chris, if you're ever thinking of getting back in,
跟我说一声 好吗?
let me know, okay?
好吗?
Yeah?
- 好的  - 很好
- Yeah.  - Good.
我根本就不理解为什么我们要这样做
I don't even know why we're doing this in the first place.
相信我 好吗? 会没事的
Just trust me, okay? It will be cool.
要是我们逃跑的话 情况会变得更糟糕
If we try to run, it will make it worse.
接货人在哪儿?
Where are these guys?
他们来了 要开始了
Here we go, here we go.
冷静点
Be cool, now.
他们来了 他们走过来了
Here we go, here we go.
嘿 哥们
Hey, man.
我们遭遇了海关突击检查 就只好把货扔进海里了
Customs boarded us, we had to dump the package.
真的丢了?
You did?
我们当时别无选择
We had no choice.
是把?
Right?
我们根本无能为力 哥们
Nothing we could do, man.
这样就行了
That's it.
就像我说的? 我跟你说过不会有事的
What did I say? I told you it was cool.
快点吧 哥们 我们赶紧离开这地方
Come on, man, let's get the fuck out of here.
喂?
Hello?
是我弟弟
It's my brother.
发生什么事了? 他没事儿吧?
What happened? Is he okay?
不 我们现在得走了
No. We've got to go now.
什么?
What?
Walter还在急救室里
Walter is in surgery.
发生什么事了 Andy?
What the fuck happened, Andy?
我们出车祸了
It was an accident.
你知道吗? 你是个差劲的骗子 快说实话吧
You know what? You're a shitty liar, so don't even fucking try.
我跟你说话的时候要看着我
Look at me when I'm talking to you.
我在走私
I was running something.
我们上船了 然后我把货扔进水里了
We got boarded, and I dumped it.
你把什么扔了?
You dumped what?
可卡因
The coke.
噢 该死
Oh, fuck.
大概超过10磅
It was over 10 pounds.
你帮谁干的?
For who?
帮Tim Briggs
For Tim Briggs
和他们那一伙
and those guys.
他们会杀了我的
They're going to kill me.
Andy 他们不会杀了你的
Andy, they're not going to kill you.
但货太多了
It was a lot of stuff.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你当然应该感到抱歉
You should be fucking sorry.
他还好吗?
Is he all right?
不好 这个小混蛋当时在走私
No, the little fuck head was running something
但把货扔了 现在是他欠别人了
and he dumped it. Now he owes.
谁? 他欠谁的?
Who? Who does he owe?
欠Tim Briggs的
Tim Briggs.
你四处打听一下 看看能不能发现什么 好吗?
Ask around, see what you can find out, all right?
Kate怎么样?
How is Kate?
不太好
Not good.
我不敢相信他竟然去走私
I can't believe he did that.
我退出的时候 我跟他说过离那些家伙远点儿
When I quit, I told him to stay away from these guys.
求你了 如果你知道些什么的话 现在就告诉我
Please, if you had anything to do with this, just tell me right now.
我都告诉你了
I just told you.
好吧
Okay.
他可是我的亲弟弟
He's my little brother.
我知道 我会想办法解决的
I know. I'm going to take care of it.
我抱你去睡觉
I got you.
我明天早上打电话给你
I'll call you in the morning.
好的 没问题
Okay, no problem.
晚安
Good night.
那按你说的 安装完这个就万无一失了吗?
So you said King Security put the system in?
没错 它确实非常有用
That's right. A lot of good it did.
这个系统运行很稳定 但是你的锁就有问题了
It's a decent system, but your locks are a joke.
任何知道防盗锁反应时间的人
Anybody who knows the response time
都能够进出一个来回
is going to be able to get in and out.
我能接个电话吗 先生?
Can you excuse me for one second, sir?
当然
Yes.
- 怎么了?  - 是关于Briggs的 他是Kyle的哥哥
- What's going on?  - It's about Briggs, Kyle's brother.
是吗 然后呢?
Yeah, and?
这我就不知道了 稍等一下
I don't know, hold on.
伙计们! 伙计们! 工程进度怎么样?
Guys! Guys! How are we doing today?
我的办公室下周能完工吗?
Is my office still going to be done last week?
你们今天早上过得不错吧?
You having a nice morning?
很好!
Good!
Briggs两个月之前刚出狱
Briggs got out of prison two months ago.
然后他就一直在Old Point酒吧附近出没
He hangs out at the Old Point Bar.
等我工作做完后就去那儿看一下 看看能不能跟他谈谈
I'll pop over there after I'm done work and see if I can talk to him.
非常抱歉 先生
Sorry about that, sir.
这些摄像头非常小
The cameras are nice and small,
它们安在墙角刚好合适
they'll fit right up there in the corner.
噢 该死!
Oh, shit!
伙计 Chris Farraday起死回生了! 不错啊!
Chris Farraday, back from the dead, man! Yeah!
看到你很高兴 哥们
Good to see you, man.
噢 该死 这家伙可是个世界级的走私贩
Oh, shit. This man was a world-class smuggler here.
你简直就是走私界的魔术师 哥们
You were fucking Houdini, man.
没错 他过去常常跟我弟弟一起干 愿上帝宽恕他那可悲的灵魂
Yeah, he used to run with my brother, God rest his miserable soul.
遗憾的是你那猪脑子内弟
Too bad your skill didn't rub off
没从你身上学到一点东西
on your shit head brother-in-law.
当然 我知道 他搞砸了
No, I know, he's a fuck up.
- 嗯  - 但是他可是我妻子的亲弟弟
- Mmm.  - But he's my wife's little brother.
我希望你能明白我们是一家人
I was hoping you understand it's family,
或许我们可以想办法解决这件事
maybe we could work something out.
呃 我不确定 你想怎么解决这件事呢?
Well, I don't know. What do you want to work out?
还是你想解决我呢?
You want to work out something with me?
我是说 我可以想办法筹钱还你货钱
I mean, I can figure out a way to pay you back the buy money.
不行 那货可值70万美元
No, that's worth 700 grand to me.
- 噢 别这样 伙计  - 不 还是你得了吧 伙计
- Oh, come on, man.  - No, come on, man.
你想让我来承担运货失败的全部责任吗?
You're going to try to charge me full freight for a bad run?
有海关上船突击检查 就把货丢了 你知道道上的规矩
Customs boards the boat, you dump that shit. You know how it goes.
你知道我当年跟你的弟弟跑了多少次货吗?
You know how many passes I gave your brother in his day?
知道 但我恨我弟弟
Yeah, I hated my brother.
你想怎么办 给我个还款计划?
What do you want to do, a payment plan?
开什么玩笑 我看着像开银行的吗?
What, do I look like a bank to you?
不 我只是希望你能在这事上讲点道理
No, I was just hoping you could be fucking reasonable, here.
嘿! 现在不是你的时代了 伙计!
Hey! This ain't your world any more, man!
你现在只不过是个过客 你不能再在这儿呼风唤雨了
You're a tourist, you can't trade on status you don't have.
我还有一大堆人要养活
I got bills to pay.
你知道的 谁搞砸的 那就是谁的麻烦
You know, when people fuck that up, that's their fucking problem.
你觉得这是儿戏吗? 你有钱吗?
You think that's funny? You got bills?
我喜欢你的衣服
I like your outfit.
我更喜欢你弟弟
I liked your brother.
我们今天又聚到一起了 这才是最重要的
We're here today, that's the important thing.
因此 大家都知道的 学着放手并让上帝
So, you know, learning to let go and let God
帮你自己从这一切中摆脱出来
is what's been pulling me through all of this.
在我杀了Briggs之前 你得想办法让我冷静下来
You're going to have to talk me down before I fucking kill Briggs.
或许你还是离开这里比较好
Probably be better off.
我总是一醉解千愁
I'm one drink away from the worst day of my life.
我现在能做点什么?
What should I do?
我也知道在这个互助会里 我不是唯一一个有这想法的人 对吧?
And I know I'm not the only one sitting in this circle that's had that same thought, right?
你要做的就是一步步来
That's all you gotta do is work the steps.
我不会再去走私了
I'm not doing another run.
绝对不会
No fucking way.
我也许能筹到启动资金 没问题的
I could probably get us the buy money, no problem.
不 我总能想到解决办法的
No, I finally got something going.
我不会冒险去重操旧业
I'm not going to chance fucking it up.
你是时代还没有过去 Chris
It's not going away, Chris.
有人想分享一下自己的经历吗?
Does somebody want to share?
Sebastian? 想跟我们分享一下你的经历吗?
Sebastian? Want to share a little bit with us?
- 好吧  - 噢 好吧
- Okay.  - Oh, yeah.
忙你的去吧
Go do your thing.
你不待在这里了吗?
You don't want to stick around?
不了 我听这种故事太容易情绪化了
No, I get far too emotional hearing that story.
- 嘿 各位 我是Sebastian  - 你好 Sebastian?
- Hey, everyone, I'm Sebastian.  - How are you doing, Sebastian?
发生什么事了?
What the hell happened?
Walter昨晚死了
Walter died last night.
Briggs来过医院了
Briggs came to the hospital.
他说了 这件事全怪我
He said it was all on me.
我一直接到电话 Chris
I keep getting calls, Chris,
还有他们一直在说会怎么折磨我
and they're talking about how they're going to fucking torture me.
我这几天就会坐船逃离这里 我不会再回来了
I'm shipping out in the next couple of days. I'm not coming back.
帮我个忙 在我走之前 不要告诉Kate
Do me a favor, and don't tell Kate. Not until I'm gone.
当我结束走私生涯的时候
When I stopped doing runs,
你向我保证过 不会染指这生意的
you promised me you were gonna stay out of this shit.
你想让我说什么 伙计?
What do you want me to say, man?
他妈的一个字都别说!
Not a fucking word!
现在搞砸了事情的可不是我 是你!
I didn't have anybody to tell me I was fucking up. You do!
还有你就想这样把你的姐姐和她的孩子们拖下水吗?
And you put your sister and the boys in this shit?
你他妈的是有什么毛病?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
喔
Whoa.
你不应该来我家的
You don't come to my fucking place.
我只是想来告诉你
I just came to tell you
我会在一个月内还你的钱
that I'm going to have your money within a month.
你只要离Andy远点就行了
Just stay away from Andy.
我可不想等那么久
I ain't waiting that long.
好吧 如果他死了 我也不会付钱的
Well, I ain't paying if he's dead.
如果背债的人死了
If a guy dies owing something
那他家里人就要替他还
his family inherits the debt.
我只给你两个星期
So I'll give you two weeks.
如果到时候你还不还钱的话 我就把你俩都干掉
If not, I'm going to come after the both of you.
然后就顺藤摸瓜
Then, all the way down the line.
我就会向你的妻子要这笔账 还有你的孩子...
I'll come asking your wife for it, your kids...
你觉得就你一个有枪吗?
Do you think you're the only guy with a fucking gun?
你会拿到钱的
You'll get your fucking money.
但如果你再敢提我的妻子
But if you ever mention my wife
和我的孩子的话 我就毙了你
and my kids again, you're done.
你听到了吗? 你他妈的就玩完了!
You hear me? You are fucking done!
爸爸
Daddy.
没事的 甜心 回屋子里去
It's okay, sweetie. Go back inside.
没事的 甜心 你爸爸和我只是在玩游戏 好吗?
It's okay, sweetie. Daddy and I were just playing, okay?
没事的 是的 我们只是在玩游戏
It's okay. Yeah, we're just playing.
没错 我和爸爸刚刚只是在玩游戏
Yeah, me and Daddy were just fucking playing.
到这里来
Get up there.
好吧 我们改天再玩儿
Yeah, we'll play again.
爸爸没事的
Daddy is okay.
没事的
It's all right.
你们他妈的在看什么?
What the fuck are you looking at?
你待在车里 我去跟她谈
You stay in the car, I'll go talk to her.
好的
Okay.
- 嘿 Chris  - 嘿 你好吗?
- Hey, Chris.  - Hey, how are you?
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
你没事吧?
Everything okay?
没事 我只想跟你说几句话
Yeah, I just wanted to talk to you for a minute.
好的
Okay.
我得跟Andy走一趟货来摆平这件事
I got to get on the ship with Andy and try to fix this.
你开什么玩笑?
Are you fucking kidding?
我还能做什么 让他一个人去吗?
What am I going to do, let him go alone?
不 我们可以想点别的办法
No, we're going to think of something else.
没有别的办法了 懂吗?
There's nothing else to do, okay?
我本来不想告诉你
I hate to tell you,
可是这件事把我们
but that little dumb fuck has put us
都拖下了水 知道吗?
in the worst possible position, okay?
如果他们不能从他身上拿到钱 他们就会找我们的麻烦
And if they don't get the money from him, they're coming after us.
你觉得我还有别的选择吗?
So what else do you want me to do?
你知道我不想做什么吗?
You know what I don't want to do?
我不想去监狱探望你 就像我们去探望你爸一样
I don't want to fucking visit you in jail like we're visiting your dad,
也不想一个人抚养那些孩子
and raising those kids on my own.
所以这是我...
So it's my...
我不想跟你争这个 可以吗?
I don't want to fight with you about this, okay?
我知道我在做什么 好吗?
I know what I'm doing, all right?
你能相信我吗?
Will you just trust me?
可以吗?
Please?
不会有事的
Nothing is going to happen.
- 好吗? 我发誓  - 嗯
- All right? I promise.  - Mmm.
Briggs那混蛋来这儿已经几年了
That shitbag Briggs was here for a couple of years.
因为他想用砖头打烂几个家伙的头
He tried to smash some guy's head in with a cinder block.
听着 我跟Sebastian说过这个
Look, I mentioned this to Sebastian.
我们要走一趟货
We're doing another run.
你能把我弄到你的旧船上吗?
Can you get me on your old boat?
你是说Borden号?
You mean the Borden?
还记得小时候你和Sebastian一起玩
Remember when you were little, you and Sebastian,
你闯进了McTier家的仓库里
you broke into McTier's warehouse,
偷走了所有狂欢节用的宝石
stole all that Mardi Gras jewelry,
你们带着一大盒珠子回家吗?
and you came back to the house with a great big box of the beads?
你还以为那是钻石
You thought they were diamonds.
你笑得就像中奖了一样
You were grinning like you just won the fucking lottery.
你还说
And you said,
"你再也不用去那船上工作了"
"You don't have to work on that boat no more."
我总会想起那件事
I always think about that.
我一生中最骄傲的一天 就是你金盆洗手的那天
The proudest day of my life was when you turned legit,
你自己开了公司 摆脱了之前的生活
and you started your own business, and you got out of the life.
我知道你必须做该做的事
I know you got to do what you got to do.
我明白
I got it.
家人就是家人
Family is family.
我会把你弄上那条船的
I'll get you on the boat.
但你进去了
But you get in,
也就一定要再出来
you got to get back out.
我和Andy要乘Borden号去巴拿马
Me and Andy are shipping out to Panama with the Borden.
你爸的船?
The old man's boat?
没错 他会把我们弄上去
Yeah, he got us on.
Camp船长怎么办?
What about Captain Camp?
我知道 我知道 别担心
I know. I know. Don't worry about it.
这是什么?
What's this?
什么是什么?
What's what?
我每次来这里 你都添置了些新家具
Every time I come here, you got new shit.
我总是要添置点东西 把房子给装修好
I'm getting it together, I'm getting the place ready.
这可是个高级咖啡桌
It's a bad-ass coffee table.
不是放鞋子的
That is not for shoes.
我必须要走了 我都不知道什么是高级了
I must be out of touch. I don't know what's bad-ass any more
因为这个看起来很便宜
because this looks cheap-ass.
你都要转型成"鸟笼"(一部电影)里的基佬了
You're turning into The Birdcage.
我是说...
I mean...
我们在巴拿马认识人吗?
So who do we know in Panama?
你要去见Ruben吗?
Are you going to go see Ruben?
兄弟 不碰毒品
Dude, no drugs.
还有谁... 还有谁能有那种利润?
What else... what else has that kind of profit margin?
Edwin在巴拿马
Edwin is in Panama.
假钞吗?
Currency?
我们要带整整一吨回来才划算
We have to bring back a shit-ton to make it worth our while.
没错 那我们就带整整一吨回来
All right, so I'll bring back a shit-ton.
行 1500万放4堆得有这么大
Okay, 15 million on four stacks this big.
跟辆Mini Cooper车差不多大
It's like the size of a Mini Cooper.
你要把东西藏在哪里?
Where are you going to hide it?
那是我的事
That's my problem.
我要Borden号的船员名单
I need the Borden's crew manifest.
噢 天呐 你在开玩笑吧
Oh, God. You got to be kidding me.
噢 我喜欢Tarik Mortin 他是个糟糕的厨子 但办起事来很不错
Oh, I like Tarik Mortin. He's a horrible chef, but he's great on runs.
Le Cloud是个烂酒鬼
Le Cloud's a fucking drunk.
Newlywed呢?
Newlywed?
办事不怎么样 但我们认识他很久了
He's not great on runs, but we've known him a long time.
Olaf技术不错 船舱里也需要人手
Olaf's solid, we need somebody in the engine room.
好吧 虽然这不是天龙特工队 但我们尽力了
Well, it's no A-Team, but it's the best we can do.
来吧 创造奇迹吧 打个电话 给我弄张工作证
Come on, work your magic. Make the call, get me a TWIC card.
嘿 亲爱的
Hi, sweet pea.
我要你给Chris Farraday弄张工作证
I need you to push through a TWIC card for Chris Farraday.
巴拿马城 巴拿马
我收到你的信息了 怎么过了三年才想起给我打电话?
I got your message. It only took you three years to call me?
你又干回老本行了?
Are you back in business?
不 没有 没有
No, no, no, no, no.
不过我需要点东西
I need something, though.
还记得我们最后一单吗? 那些假钞?
Remember our last run? The funny money?
下个星期之前 给我一批一模一样的货 不过要更多
I need that exact same shit by next week, but a lot more.
四倍的量
Four times as much.
我们要一个足够大的小货车运货 可以吗?
And we need a van big enough to transport it, okay?
可以 我这就去
Okay. I'll be here.
加油 Mikey!
Come on, Mikey!
有趣的钱是什么?
What's funny money?
什么? 没什么 就是爸爸工作上的事
Huh? Nothing. That's just work stuff for Dad.
你曾被判有间谍罪吗?
Have you ever been convicted of espionage?
只要回答"有"或者"没有" 走下流程 很快就好了
Just answer yes or no, we'll get through this really quickly.
没有
No.
煽动罪 串谋犯间谍罪 叛国罪呢?
Sedition, or conspiracy to commit espionage, sedition, treason?
一起的吗?
Together?
我收到了您的装运申请书 您是...
I received your shipping application, Mr...
我叫Lakowski
Lakowski.
Lakowski先生
Mr. Lakowski.
Lakowski先生 我给您一个20英尺高的干货标准集装箱
Se?or Lakowski, I'm getting you a 20-foot standard dry.
您需要我们装货吗?
Would you like us to load it?
不需要 那个我已经让别人负责了 我就是想要集装箱
No, I've got somebody to take care of that. I just need the container.
好的 我们会将为您准备的
Okay, we'll leave the container
集装箱放在巴拿马港口
standing by for you at the port of Panama.
您要运送什么?
And what are you shipping?
一辆小货车
A van.
给你
Here you go.
赚钱之前要投钱啊 宝贝
It takes money to make money, baby.
谢谢
Thank you.
坐船别沉了 爸爸
Don't sink, Daddy.
当然了 宝贝
Okay, buddy.
你不能去看我的季后赛了
You're going to miss my playoff game.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
你妈妈会拍很多照片给我看的 好吗?
Your mom is going to take lots of pictures for me, okay?
在我回来之前 你们就是管事儿的
You guys are in charge till I get back.
我爱你们
I love you, guys.
平安回来 好吗?
Just come home, okay?
谢谢你 Chris
Thank you for doing this, Chris.
- 我爱你  - 我也爱你
- I love you.  - Love you, too.
会没事的
It's going to be okay.
请出示身份证 把手指放在扫描仪上
ID, please. Finger on the scanner.
- Camp船长  - 把行李箱拿来
- Captain Camp.  - Get the trunk.
把船长的地毯清洁器拿上架桥
Get that Captain's carpet cleaner up to the bridge.
LO John 你能帮我一把吗?
LO John, you want to give me a hand?
嗨!
Hey!
你睡上铺 我睡下铺
You're up top. I get the bottom bunk.
好的 没问题
Yeah, no kidding.
别装得你讨厌这破事儿一样
Don't act like you don't like this shit.
我表现得那么明显吗?
Why, is it that obvious?
我喜欢这活儿 不过别告诉你姐姐
I love it, but don't tell your sister.
好了 走了 晚点再睡你的美容觉吧 我们走
All right, come on. You can get your beauty rest later, let's go.
我的胳膊 小心
My arm, my arm.
留心点
Keep an eye out.
嘿 有人来了
Hey, someone's coming.
还好吗? Chris
What's up, Chris?
嗨 Chris
Hi, Chris.
是你啊 Chris
Chris.
瞧瞧这混蛋
Look at this motherfucker.
Olaf 见到你太好了 兄弟
Olaf. Good to see you, man.
你好啊 Tarik 你还好吗?
What's up, Tarik? You okay?
你好啊 兄弟
What's up, man?
- 你父母怎么样? 大家都好吗?  - 很好 很好
- How's your folks? Everybody's good?  - Good, good.
看来你肯定是饿惨了
That's a hungry man's appetite.
这很好吃
This is real good.
还好吗? 兄弟
How you doing, buddy?
你在我船上干嘛?
What the fuck are you doing on my ship?
你检查船员名单了吗?
Did you even check the goddamn crew manifest?
你怎么能让Farraday上我的船?
How the fuck do you let Bud Farraday's spawn aboard my ship?
国土安全部检查过了 是他在最后一分钟加上名单的...
DHS cleared him. He was added at the last minute...
好吧 我已经把他降级为服务生了
All right, I'm demoting him to ship's boy.
是 船长
Yes, sir.
你去把灰擦一擦 别他妈再让我看见你
You scrub dirt and stay the fuck out of my sight.
否则你会有意外的
Otherwise you might have an accident,
然后在海里了结你的小命
and wind up in the drink.
告诉他地毯清洁器在哪里
Show him where the carpet cleaner is.
是 船长
Yes, sir.
噢 天呐 地毯清洁器
Oh, man, carpet cleaner.
走吧 擦地毯专家
Let's go, Rug Doctor.
噢 你升职了? 他们又给你加了几道新的杠杠
Oh, you got promoted? They gave you some new stripes on there.
我是服务生 你仍然是船长的狗腿子
I'll be ship's boy. You're still Captain's bitch boy.
是啊 是啊
Yeah, yeah.
好的
Okay.
是 船长
Yes, sir.
所有人都在喝酒 没人工作
Everybody's drinking tall boys, and nobody's fucking working.
你好啊 伙计
What's up, man?
船长算是我们一伙儿的吗?
Are you bringing the Captain in on this or what?
当然没有
Fuck, no.
我还记得在就在这个房间跟你爸说过话
Well, I remember talking to your pops in this same room.
他说了一样的屁话 我们都知道结果如何
He said that same shit. We know how that turned out.
你们相信我吗?
Do you trust me or not?
相信 当然
I do. I do.
我们运什么货?
So what are we running?
5000张还没裁剪过的"超级美元"
A shipping pallet loaded up with 5,000 uncut sheets of super notes.
那可是能买到的最好假钞
Best counterfeit money can buy.
你怎么就认为我们能运那么多东西呢?
And just how the hell do you think we're going to stow that much shit?
你是担心了吗 兄弟? 我是说 信仰在哪里?
You worried, buddy? I mean, where is the faith?
怎么 因为我降了级? 现在我就要从头开始了吗?
What, I lost my stripes? Now I got to start from scratch?
确实 那东西是空的
Exactly, that shit's void.
那没关系
No problem.
来 我给你们看
Come on, I'll show you.
觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
看起来不错 Chris 你是个疯子
Looks good. Chris, you're a crazy fucker.
这不错 是吗? 六十立方英尺
Not bad? Huh? Sixty cubic feet.
根本不止 这比六十立方英尺大
No fucking way. No, it's bigger than 60.
啊 该死! 是啊 兄弟 这比六十立方英尺大多了
Ah, shit! Yeah, man, this is much bigger than 60.
有人来了
We got company.
快 快 放回去!
Quick, quick, quick!
嘿 你做什么呢? Chris 停下来!
Hey, what are you doing? Chris, stop!
Andy 在里面安静点
Andy, be quiet in there.
快 快!
Come on, come on!
你们在这干嘛?
What the hell are you doing in here?
我要一把刮刀 我们发现较低的船体发霉了
I needed a scraper. We noticed some mold in the lower hull.
漂白剂没用 所以...
The bleach wasn't cutting it, so...
你们不应该来这附近 快走吧
Well, you shouldn't be dicking around in here. Get going.
我就是想帮你弄干净点 头儿
I was just trying to keep it clean for you, boss.
嘿 Chris! Chris!
Hey, Chris! Chris!
举起来! 举起来! 加油 你可以的!
Bring it right back up! Come on, you got it!
你可以的 加油!
You got it, come on!
我不行了
I can't do it.
该死
God damn.
你来举吗?
Are you getting on?
不了
No.
你要我再把你送到箱子里吗?
Do you want me to put you back in the box?
这不好笑
That's not funny.
我可能会闷死在那个箱子里的
I could have suffocated in that box.
"我可能会..."
"I really could have..."
别逗那孩子了 兄弟
Leave the kid alone, man.
你打算怎么做这事?
How are you going to pull this shit off?
- 我们要运大约300个集装箱  - 嗯
- We're delivering 300 or so containers.  - Yeah.
我们至少要在那边装500个 我们不会在港口呆那么久
We're picking up 500 or more. We're not going to be in port that long.
我们要开车去Chorrillo 跟Edwin碰面 装上货
So we got to drive out to Chorrillo, see Edwin, load up the bills,
然后在高峰拥挤时段开车回船上
and then drive back to the boat during rush hour.
时间会很紧迫 但我们能搞定
It's going to be tight, but we're going to be good.
这会非常紧迫 时间卡得太紧了
It's going to be too tight. We're cutting it close.
可能时间会不够
Might not have enough time.
我们就拖延时间
We'll buy more time.
有可变螺距推进器
Controllable pitch propeller.
噢 是啊 有螺距推进器
Oh, yeah. Pitch propeller.
你能把供油排干吗?
Can you drain the oil supply?
那是液压油箱会失灵的
The hydraulic chamber won't work.
那是才重点 笨蛋
That's the point, stupid ass.
听着
Look.
别人把船拖过船闸的时候 我们就可以动手
We can do it while being towed through the locks.
这能拖延几个小时
It will buy us a couple of hours.
- 行吗?  - 我不知道
- Okay?  - I don't know.
我讨厌把船弄坏
I hate when we fuck with the boat.
你说什么?
What?
我说我讨厌把船弄坏
I said, I hate when we fuck with the boat.
放松点 大块头
Take it easy, big bear.
Olaf 操他妈的船
Olaf, fuck with the boat.
放松点 放松
Take it easy. Easy.
怎么了?
What the fuck?
Tarik 那混蛋会活吃了你
Tarik. That motherfucker will eat you.
好了 下车了
Okay, out you come.
- 能帮我拿点东西吗?  - 一定要拿吗?
- Do you want to get any of these for me?  - Do we have to?
可以啊 妈妈
Yes, Mom.
可以吗? 很好
Yeah? Okay.
是谁?
Hello?
需要帮忙吗?
Can I help you?
你真美
You're pretty.
想玩玩吗?
Do you want to play?
行了 再见 混蛋
Okay. Bye, asshole.
还钱 你欠我的
Pay the money just like you owe me.
你们都在看什么?
What the fuck are you all looking at?
你喜欢这样吗?
Yeah, you like that?
把你的脏手拿开!
Get your fucking hands off me!
把刀放下 把刀放下
Come on, put the knife down. Put the knife down.
把刀放下
Put the knife down.
放开我妈咪!
Leave my mommy alone!
都给我回去! 坐好了!
Get the fuck back over there! Sit your fucking ass down!
没事 我在玩儿呢
It's okay, I'm just playing, now.
我就是玩玩
I'm just playing.
别这样 别哭
Yeah, don't cry.
你们之前见过枪吗? 想要吗?
You seen a gun before? You want it?
我下个星期再来的时候 可就不是玩玩的了
There ain't going to be no playing when I come back next week.
你可以告诉你丈夫
You can tell your husband that.
- 想试试吗?  - 滚开!
- You want this?  - Get out!
- 不!  - 你干了什么?
- No!  - What the fuck?
都他妈滚出去! 滚出我的屋子!
Get the fuck out of my house! Get the fuck out of my house!
把那东西放下!
Put that thing down, man!
你不会认为现在警察会来吧?
You don't think the police are going to be coming now?
快滚出去!
Get the fuck out of here!
我没想开枪打他 是那小混蛋的错
I didn't mean to shoot at him. The little shit hit the gun.
你想把我送回乡下吗? 你这个愚蠢的婊子
You want to send me back to the farm, you stupid bitch?
噢 天呐 噢 天呐
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, God.
巴拿马运河 斯水闸
好了 注意点 别太多
All right, careful. Not too much.
- 我们不想把这弄堵塞了  - 明白
- We don't want to jam it.  - I got it
Chris Farraday 到架桥上来
Chris Farraday, to the bridge.
给
Here.
他正过去
He's on his way.
别太多
Not too much.
好的
All right.
你的手机打不通
I wasn't getting reception on your cell.
Chris 那些人来过我们家了 他... 他们有枪
Chris, these guys came to the house. They... they had guns.
天呐 你还好吗? 孩子们还好吗?
Jesus, are you okay? Are the boys okay?
我们还好 就是吓坏了
Yeah, we're okay. We're freaked out.
我觉得其中一个是Tim Briggs 就是Kyle的哥哥
I think one of them was Tim Briggs, Kyle's brother.
我没有报警 我不想警察来这问东问西的
I didn't call the police, I don't want them here asking questions.
好的 我知道了
Yeah, okay, I will.
没事的 我爱你 记得打电话
All right, I love you. Call him.
老婆出什么事了吗 Farraday?
Trouble with the missus, Farraday?
你想我替你安慰一下她吗?
Do you want me to talk to her for you?
嘿 小家伙 你们还好吗? 今天够吓人的啊?
Hey, guys, you okay? You had a scary day?
是的
Mmm-hmm.
要不这样? 你们都搬到我家来
You know what? Why don't you guys
住一段时间 怎么样?
just come and stay at my place?
他们估计不会再来了 但这能让我放心点
They're not going to be back, but just for my own peace of mind.
你真这么觉得?
You think?
真的? 好的吧
Really? Okay.
减速前行
Slow ahead.
我说了 减速前行! 速度减半!
I said, slow ahead! Reduce to half speed!
为什么我们还没减速?
Why are we not slowing down?
油压下降
Oil pressure's down.
好的 看着点那温度显示器
All right. Keep an eye on that temperature.
全速后退!
Full astern!
全速后退 船长
Full astern, Captain.
- 什么事 船长?  - 全速后退!
- Yeah, Captain?  - Full astern!
我们他妈的要撞上那码头了!
We're going to hit the fucking dock!
我在试了 但没反应 螺旋桨卡住了!
I'm trying, but I got no pitch control. The fucking prop is jammed!
你抽掉太多机油了! 我可没想让你把船给弄沉了!
You drained too much oil out! I didn't want you to crash the boat!
什么?
What?
拜托! 我这里一点油压都没有!
Come on! I'm not getting any oil pressure!
抛下左舷锚!
Let go the port anchor!
天呐 该死...
Jesus, fucking...
他妈的快抛下左舷锚!
Let go the fucking port anchor!
它没动! 你松开闸门了吗?
It's not moving! Did you release the brake?
闪开! 走开!
Get out of the way! Move!
右转舵!
Turn starboard!
太晚了! 左转舵 Luke! 左转舵!
It's too late! Hard to port, Luke! Hard to port!
我去把引擎给熄了!
I'm going to have to kill the engine!
该死...
Fucking...
要撞上了!
We're going to hit!
这里他妈的发生什么事了?
What the fuck is going on around here?
他妈的出了什么情况?
What the fuck happened?
螺旋桨卡住了
Propeller jam.
肯定有人搞破坏
Someone tampered with it.
我不这么觉得
I don't think so.
肯定有人搞破坏
Someone tampered with it.
你机械部门谁管事的?
他第一次上班吗? 还是他醉过去了?
你呢? 你睡着了吗?
请原谅我
这种事情下次不准再发生!
知道了
好吧 好吧
机油的事情真不好意思
Sorry about that oil thing.
别担心那个
Don't worry about it.
这还给我们争取了点时间
It will buy us a little more time.
嘿 Michael 快看 那个看起来就像是宇宙飞船
Hey, Michael, look. It's like a spaceship over here.
Sebastian 这里太漂亮了
Wow, Sebastian, it's amazing in here.
是吗? 大有改观 对吧?
Yeah? It's coming along, right?
我都忘了 装修之后你就没有来过
I forgot you haven't been here since the renovation.
嘿 别碰那东西
Hey, don't touch that.
小家伙们 帮我拿一下这个
Fellas, you hang on to this.
好的 好极了
Okay, that's good.
瞄得好
Good aim.
嘿 一切都还好吧?
Hey, everything okay?
是啊 我们在Sebastian家里
Yeah we're at Sebastian's.
孩子们都没事吗?
Are the boys okay?
没事 你已经到巴拿马了?
Yeah. Are you in Panama already?
是的 手机记得随身带
Yeah. Keep your phone on you.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你 我等会儿再打电话给你
I love you, too. I'll call you on my way back.
我们快到了
We're almost there.
进来
Entrar.
嘿! 哇哦!
Hey! Whoa!
你这儿猫真多
You got a lot of pussy in here.
见到你太好了 朋友
Good to see you, man.
- 都还好吧?  - 是啊
- Everything good?  - Yeah.
好的 那钱和车子准备好了?
Good, you got the cash, the van?
- 是的 是的  - 很好
- Si, si.  - Cool.
好的
Yeah.
去把车开过来
哇哦
Whoa.
怎么了 你不相信我?
What, you don't trust me?
噢 我当然相信你
Oh, I trust you.
Está bueno?
好货?
不对 这绝对不是好货
No, it's no fucking bueno.
Andy 你等在这里 Danny 过来
Andy, wait here. Danny, come on.
嘿 怎么了? 你在找什么?
Hey, what is it? What are you doing?
我需要些碘酒
I need some iodine.
墨水是光变油墨 层次也是对的
The ink is OVI, the layers are right,
但这纸张感觉不对
but that paper felt different.
Hey, qué pasa? What's going on?
嘿 出什么事了? 怎么了?
最好是我弄错了
You better hope I'm wrong.
他妈你们这群白痴印在了带淀粉的纸上了
You fucking idiots didn't print this on starch-free paper.
对不住了 朋友 这是我最好的货色了
I'm sorry, man. This is the best I have.
我没时间跟你吵
I don't have time for this.
我电话上跟你说了
I told you on the phone,
我要跟上次一模一样的货
I needed exactly what you sold me last time.
Gonzalo有 Gonzalo仓库里有一模一样的
Gonzalo. Gonzalo has it at the warehouse.
Gonzalo? 那个替Heraeus打工的小滑头?
Gonzalo? That little shithead who works for Heraeus?
不是 Heraeus已经不在了
No. There's no more Heraeus.
现在Gonzalo管事了
Gonzalo is running things now.
那你为什么不一开始就把我带到他那里去?
Why didn't you send me to him in the first place?
你在耍我吗? 你他妈是在玩我吧...
Are you fucking playing games with me? Are you fucking playing...
我试过了! 但他不想有人去那里!
I tried! But he doesn't want anybody going there!
不行 不行
No, no, no.
我们这就去那仓库 走吧
We're going to the warehouse. Let's go.
不行 不行 不行
No, no, no, no, no.
Chris 等等
Chris.
嘿 Chris 伙计 你把车开走吧 真对不起
Hey, Chris, man, look, take the van, man. I'm sorry.
快跑 Mikey!
Come on, Mikey!
天呐 太阳晒死我了
Man, the sun's really killing me.
- 那小子好大个  - 是啊
- That kid is big.  - He is.
那11号长得好大个
Number 11 is a big kid.
你拿一下 我要接个电话
Hold on, I got to take this.
好的
Okay.
喂 伙计 怎么了?
Hey, man, what's up?
他没把货准备好
He didn't have them.
好吧
All right.
那我想 你得带点好东西回来了
Well, I guess you're going to have to bring in some candy.
我不带毒品的
I'm not bringing in drugs.
你还是去找Ruben吧
Just go and see Ruben.
我跟你说过 我不带毒品的 好吗 这没得商量
I told you, I'm not bringing in drugs. Okay. It's not an option.
Chris Chris Chris 我求你了 求你了
Chris, Chris, Chris, I'm begging you. Please.
Chris? 在吗 Chris?
Chris? Yeah, Chris?
把他给我塞进车里面
Put him in the fucking van.
你知道的 要是你空着手回来的话
You know, you come back empty-handed,
Andy就死定了
Andy's going to get fucking hit,
你他妈还是要弄出那多钱来
and you're still gonna have to come up with the goddamn money.
我会解决的 好吗?
Look, I'll figure it out, okay?
让Brigg那群家伙离我家人远点 求你了
Just keep Briggs away from my family, please.
好的 没问题
Yeah, of course.
嘿 我工作上出了点问题 我要去解决一下
Hey, I got a little problem at work I got to take care of.
待会见了 伙计们
See you later, buddy.
- 再见 Sebastian  - 没事吧?
- Bye, Sebastian.  - Everything okay?
没事 都没问题 你有门钥匙吧?
Yeah, everything's fine. You got your key?
有的
Yeah.
我跟你说 朋友 离Gonzalo远点
I'm telling you, man. Stay away from Gonzalo.
自从他管事起 他就疯得很
He's been acting crazy lately, since he became a boss.
离他远点
Stay away from him.
Chris 我们应该听他的
Chris, we should have listened to him.
我们不到一个小时就要上船了 时间来不及的
We got less than an hour to get back to the boat. It ain't going to work.
会成功的
It will work.
我说 你知道Gonzalo的仓库在哪里吗?
I mean, do you even know where Gonzalo's warehouse is?
我们现在就在Chorrillo了
We're in fucking Chorrillo right now.
我看周围有什么能让我想起来的
I'm looking for something to remind me.
我们会找到的
We're going to find it.
就这儿了 就这儿了 快看 就是这里! 这里!
Here we go. Here we go. Look, right here! Here!
- Mortin  - 怎么了 船长?
- Mortin.  - Yeah, Cap?
Farraday这家伙去哪里了?
Where the hell is Farraday?
我不知道 船长
I don't know, Cap.
我不知道今天我得看着他 小本子上没写啊
I didn't know I had to babysit him today. I didn't get the memo.
别跟我耍花腔 Mortin
Don't piss me off, Mortin.
不然你连说"底薪"的机会都没有
You'll be flipping shit-burgers at McDonald's
直接去麦当劳给我包汉堡去
before you can say "minimum wage."
对不起 船长 对不起
I'm sorry, Cap. Sorry.
你是不是去骚扰过Kate和孩子们了 就是Chris的家人?
That little visit you paid Kate, the kids, Chris' family?
那也是我家人
That's my family.
你离他们远点 听清楚了吗?
You stay away from them. Are we clear?
嗨 Sadie
Hi, Sadie.
嗨
Hi.
听清楚了 如果你要叫个在行的去走私 不叫Andy去的话
You know, if you had hired a real smuggler instead of Andy,
我们的货早就按时到手了
our package would have come in when it was supposed to.
听着 出这种事非常抱歉
You know, I'm really sorry about that.
你知道现在这事他妈赖我头上了吗?
Do you know how fucked up things are for me right now?
我知道 他说过他知道自己在做什么的
I know. He said he knew what he was doing.
我不知道他是他的姐夫啊
I didn't know he was his brother-in-law.
嘿 伙计 这个和我们
Hey, man, this is way more high-risk
之前的计划相比也太危险了吧
than I originally anticipated.
我可是有老婆的 我爱我老婆
I got a wife now. I like my wife.
是啊 我也有老婆的 好吧?
Yeah, I got a wife, too, okay?
别担心Gonzalo这人
And don't worry about Gonzalo.
我认识他 他就他妈是个小混混 别担心
I know him, he's a little fucking punk. Don't worry about it.
哦 是吗? 我听说这家伙
Oh, yeah? I heard stories about this dude
可是会把人头砍掉的
cutting people's heads off and shit.
我找Gonzalo有事
I'm looking for Gonzalo.
左转!
Andy 呆在车子里看着钱
Andy, stay in the van with the bag.
Danny 没事的 我认识这个人 快点
Danny, it's all good. I know this guy, come on.
你有一条新消息
You have one new message.
嘿 小瘪三 我现在在看你外甥踢足球呢
Hey, fuckhead, I'm watching your sister's kid play soccer.
你要是不回我电话
You don't call me back,
我就走过去朝他脑袋开一枪
I'm gonna walk out on that field and put a bullet in his head.
跟Gonzalo说 Chris Farraday在找你
带他们过来
知道了 老大
让这狗闭嘴! 快点 拉走
跟我来
是你啊 Chris
Chris.
闭... 闭嘴
Don't... stop talking.
照我说的做 我要你拿着
Like I said, I want you to take
那付账的钱去这个地址
the buy money and go to that address,
和一个叫Ruben的人谈谈
and talk to a gentleman named Ruben.
如果你还想再看到你的小外甥的话
If you ever want to see your little nephew again,
你就乖乖拿着货 然后带回来 懂了吗?
you take the package and you bring it back, all right?
嘿 这是头狼吗?
Hey, is that a wolf?
肯定不是条狗
That ain't no fucking dog.
先生 打扰一下 行吗?
Excuse me, senor. Do you mind?
他在哪里?
Where is he?
我老朋友Farraday在哪里啊?
Where is my old friend Farraday?
把车子开进来
Bring the van around.
没打招呼就过来了 真不好意思
Sorry for showing up unannounced.
Edwin想耍我
Edwin was trying to play games with me.
Herseus在哪儿呢?
Where's my buddy Herseus?
我们把他喂狼了
We fed him to the wolves.
什么 说真的?
What, literally?
I am the new Herseus, cabrón.
我就是新的Herseus 伙计
能见到你真好啊
It's good to see you.
我也是
You, too.
你觉得怎么样?
What do you think?
这些都是我的了
It's all mine, motherfucker.
那群以为我是垃圾的混蛋?
All those assholes who thought I was shit?
他们都死得快长虫子了
They're dead por culeros.
我们打算劫辆卡车
We're taking down a truck.
大家伙 武装卡车
It's a big one. An armored truck.
你要一起来吗?
Do you want to join us?
你开玩笑的吧?
Are you serious?
Andy 你在哪?
Andy?
Andy 回话!
Andy!
噢 该死
Oh, fuck.
Andy 回话!
Andy!
- Andy在解决了 跟Rubben说一声  - 知道了
他在前插...
He charges...
Michael 别乱跑 我们是客人
Michael, not in the house. We're guests.
看看老爸年轻的样子
Look at young Daddy.
射门了!
He shoots!
球进了!
He scores!
去找你妈妈
Go find your mom.
你不是说笑的吧? 看上去你都准备好了
You ain't fucking around, huh? Looks like you're ready for anything.
你要准备打仗还是怎么着?
Are you going to war or something?
我跟你说了 我们要劫卡车 他妈就是这样
I told you. We're taking down a truck. Fucking rock and roll.
利索 你都找了这帮人了
No shit. You got all these guys.
那卡车里是什么东西 伙计?
What the fuck is in that truck, man?
你想知道?
You want to know?
那你可能要现场教一下这群混蛋怎么打劫了
Then maybe you should show these assholes how it's done.
算了 听着...
No, look...
我免费给你这些超级美元
I'll give you the super notes for free.
谢谢啦 但我还要赶着上船 所以...
Yeah, thanks anyway. But I got a boat to catch, so...
拜托 别告诉我你不想干这种事
Come on. Don't tell me you don't miss this shit.
我有两个小鬼了 伙计 你知道吗? 随我乱来的日子已经结束了
I got two kids now, man, you know? My cowboy days are over.
快点 Danny!
Come on, Danny!
钱不见了
The money's gone.
Andy也不见了
And Andy.
什么?
What?
你他妈在说什么?
What the fuck are you talking about?
你就这么过来把我当白痴耍吗?
You come in here and treat me like an asshole?
不可能 我不会这么做的 伙计
No, primo, I wouldn't do that, man.
我真应该把你脑子打开花
I should fucking blow your brains out.
你刚刚的话还算数吗?
Does that offer still stand?
我们和你一起去劫车 货就免费给我?
We ride with you, I get the super notes for free?
是的 你对我们还有点用处
Yeah, there's something you can do for us.
把他们的钱包缴了
Grab their wallets.
把你的钱包给他
Give him your wallet.
把他们的身份证给我
Give me their IDs.
我们停在这里 就是要按分钟罚钱的 船长
We're being fined every minute longer we sit here, Captain.
我知道
Yep.
我们需要把...
We got to take that...
- 船长  - 情况怎么样了?
- Captain.  - What's the status?
变距螺旋桨过热 需要机油 我们正在解决这问题
Pitch propeller overheated. It needs oil. We're working on it.
给你10分钟!
You got 10 minutes!
是Olaf
It's Olaf.
Chris 你就只有10分钟时间
Chris, you have got 10 minutes.
这点时间根本不够
That's not long enough.
让Tarik拖延装货时间
Have Tarik delay the loading.
你就尽力拖住他们 好吗?
Just stall them for as long as you can, okay?
快点 我尽力而为
Get here. I'll do what I can.
看到了吧 Chris? 这正是我最不想看到的情况
See, Chris? This is exactly what I didn't want to happen.
一模一样
Exactly.
我们在这里干什么呢?
I mean, what are we supposed to be doing here?
挡住卡车
Blocking the truck.
是啊 好极了
Right. That's awesome.
我们要去挡卡车
We're blocking the truck.
就像碰碰车一样
Like human speed bumps.
跟我老婆说...
Tell my wife that...
你他妈能闭嘴吗?
Will you shut the fuck up?
听着 我们能挺过去的 知道吗?
Look, we're going to get through this, okay?
我什么话都不会和你老婆说的!
I'm not telling your wife shit!
好吧 准备好 他们来了
Okay, ready. They're coming.
系上安全带
Put your seatbelt on.
他们下来了 该我们了
He's coming down. Here we go.
他会刹车吗?
Is he going to slow down?
是的 他会刹车的
Yeah, he's going to slow down.
- 你说他会刹车的!  - 他会刹车的
- You said he's going to slow down!  - He's gonna slow down.
他才没刹车呢!
He's not slowing down!
该死!
Shit!
Fuck!
你还好吧?
Are you all right?
这里是220号运钞车
我们遭到袭击了
天呐
Oh, my God.
哦 我靠!
Oh, fuck!
趴下!
Get down!
Danny 你没事吧?
Danny, are you okay?
让我看看
对 就是这个
我们得把木架拿掉
你先帮我留着D E F三个集装箱 等我说好了你再装
I need you to hold containers D, E and F, until I say so.
我给你100美元 行吧?
I'm going to pay you $100, yeah?
快点 警察来了
你们这是在耍我吗!
You got to be fucking kidding me!
该死!
Fuck!
Chris 快趴下!
Get down, Chris!
操!
Fuck!
把车子开过来!
快开过来!
坚持住
Hold on.
伙计 我们这是在干什么?
What the fuck are we doing, dude?
等一下!
Wait, wait, wait!
该死的 快开过来!
快来!
Come on!
可恶!
Shit!
各自就位 别让任何人跑了
快! Danny 起来 我们得走了!
Shit! Danny, come on, we're going!
快点 Danny 我们走! 该死!
Come on, Danny, let's go! Shit!
快追!
操!
Fuck!
现在怎么办?
What now?
该死!
Fuck!
D E F三组装载得慢了
告诉协调组
叫他们快点 我们还有别的船要进港
Andy 你知道Chris在哪儿吗?
Andy, where's Chris?
嘿Andy!
Andy!
Gonzalo回来了!
快 把门打开!
快点 我们得走了!
Come on, we got to move!
你干什么?
What are you doing?
我们得拿回ID卡
We got to get our IDs.
- 医院  - 天呐!
- Hospital.   - Oh, shit!
赶快带我去医院
Take me to the fucking hospital.
该死 Danny 来帮忙
Oh, shit. Danny, help.
快 躺下
Come on, lay down.
抓住他!
Hold him, hold him!
快点 我们赶紧离开这!
该死! 他死了吗?
Oh, shit! Is he dead?
他死了!
He's dead!
要是他死了 就把他扔出去
If he's fucking dead, throw him out the van.
等等! 拿着我们的ID卡!
Wait, wait! Get our IDs!
- 拿到了吗?   - 拿到了
- You got them?  - Yeah.
把他扔出去!
Toss him out!
好了 伙计们 启动发动机
Okay, boys, let's warm her up.
你觉得我们还剩下多少时间?
How much time do you think we have?
没时间了
No time.
我们要走了 快点把那几个集装箱装载上船
Get those containers aboard or we're leaving without them.
Chris 你们在哪儿? 船要走了
Chris, where the fuck are you, man? The ship's leaving.
拖住船 我们马上就到
Just hold the ship, we're coming.
给我快点过来!
Just get your ass over here!
好的
All right.
对于任何还没上来的船员
Any crew member hasn't come aboard yet,
你得先搜身
you make sure they get searched
才能让他们上船 知道了吗?
before you let them on, you got me?
加把劲 就快到了
All right, come on, it's going to open up.
我们能行吗?
Are we going to make it?
行的 他在为我们拖延装载集装箱
Yeah, he's holding the container for us.
快点 快啊快啊!
Come on. Go, go, go!
我到了 打开集装箱
I'm coming. Open the container.
船开了以后 放我们出来的时候带些工具清洗一下车子
When you come to let us out, bring something to clean up a bit of a mess.
- 别忘了防水封袋!   - 知道了
- Don't forget the seals!  - Okay.
该死
Shit.
好了 可以装载了
Yeah, yeah. Here we go.
别他妈挡我的道!
Get the fuck out of the way!
快点 给我滚进去!
Come on, get your ass in here!
- 该死!  - 操!
- Fuck!  - Fuck!
可恶!
Shit!
等等 停下!
Wait, stop!
不会吧!
Come on!
我靠 这门还开着!
The fucking doors are open!
该死!
Oh, fuck!
我能关上
I got it.
天哪!
Oh, fuck!
等等 你慌什么?
Hold up. What's the rush?
没什么
Come on.
我只是去拿落了的食物 知道吗? 别这样 Jack
I just left some food on, you know? Come on, Jack.
船长下令搜查所有下船的员工
Captain has got us searching everybody that got off.
嘿 你去哪儿?
Hey, where are you going?
我刚藏了些不错的牛肉
I just stowed some decent beef.
哦! 谢天谢地
Ooh! Thank God.
你昨晚做得东西太难吃了
That shit you made last night was like chewing ass.
哈哈 今天的保你满意
Yeah, you would know.
去你的 Tarik
Fuck you, Tarik.
快点
Come on.
- 你带清洗工具了吗?   - 带了
- You got the cleaning stuff?  - Yeah.
- 密封袋呢?  - 带了
- You got the seals?  - Yeah.
抓紧时间 我们上来得太晚了 他们肯定要检查这箱的
All right, we got on late they're definitely going to check this.
天哪!
Holy shit!
我们开始吧
Let's go, baby.
好的
Will do.
船长 海关局那边的电话
Customs and Border Protection, Captain.
他们想让我们检查一下那几个晚点装船的集装箱
They want us to take a look at some containers that were loaded late.
好的 我们去看一下
All right, let's go.
马上就去
Call in the Second.
快点 Danny 我们走
Let's go, Danny. Let's go.
我们要看哪几个 队长?
Where are we looking, Chief?
那边那个集装箱 船长
The container right up here, Captain.
812504号
812504.
812...
不好意思 船长
Sorry, Captain.
下一个
Next.
可恶
Oh, shit.
- 我去看一下散热盘...  - 等等!
- I'm gonna check the heating coils...  - Wait, wait!
我过几分钟再回来
I'm gonna need a couple of minutes.
快点 快走
Come on, let's go.
2727号箱子
2727.
812729号
812729.
- 哦!  - 该死 有老鼠!
- Oh!  - Shit, rats!
关起来!
Shut it!
当心手
Watch your hand.
嘿!
Yo, yo, yo!
我们这儿有污水泄漏 叫Brody来一下 好吧?
We got a sewage leak. Call Brody, all right?
可以了 开始吧
All right, let's go.
这上面还有两个集装箱
We got two more containers up here.
Nathan812552号
Nathan 812552,
和812553号
812553.
就是这个 打开它
That's it, open it.
这是525524号
525524.
这是最后一个上船的集装箱
That's the last container that was boarded.
看看
Go on.
有什么发现吗?
Anything?
没有 先生 闻起来好像刚被清理过
No, sir. Smells like it was just cleaned.
好吧 封起来
All right, seal it up.
到了以后海关会接手
Customs will take it apart when we get back home.
我有话和你说...
I need to tell you...
你他妈脑子不好使了吗?
Are you out of your fucking mind?
还是你本来就没脑子?
Are you fucking crazy?
钱呢? 钱在哪儿?
Where's the money? Where is it?
花掉了! 我迫不得已的
It's gone! I had to use it.
什么? 钱在哪儿?
It's what? Where's the money?
你想要什么...
What are you trying to...
你刚说什么?
What did you just say to me?
我迫不得已用掉了
I had to use it.
你什么?
You what?
我不得不这么做
I had to use it.
在天花板上
It's in the ceiling.
不 你真该死...
No, you fucking...
你是有多蠢啊?
How fucking stupid are you?
我这么大老远的过来帮你 冒了这么大的风险
I came out here to help you, to risk my fucking freedom
还要连累我的妻儿 就为了运毒?
and my wife and my children for this?
你个混账东西
Motherfucker.
你说我他妈该怎么处理这东西?
What the fuck am I supposed to do with all that?
你真是蠢到家了...
You got to be the dumbest motherfucker...
他威胁说要杀了Michael
He said he was going to kill Michael.
什么?
What?
你有一条留言信息
You have one saved message.
嘿 小瘪三 我现在在看你外甥踢足球呢
Hey, fuckhead, I'm watching your sister's kid play soccer.
你要是不回我电话
You don't call me back,
我就走过去朝他脑袋开一枪
I'm gonna walk out on that field and put a bullet in his head.
拿好袋子
Get the bag.
- 你还好吗?  - 是的
- Are you all right?  - Yeah.
怎么样? 没事吧?
You all right? You all right?
嗯嗯 我没事
Yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
抱歉 冷静 我们先冷静一下
I'm sorry. Calm down, calm down.
- Chris  - 嘿
- Chris.  - Hey.
你没事吧? 孩子们还好吗?
Everything okay? Boys all right?
挺好的 他们睡着了
Yeah, they're sleeping.
怎么了? 你还好吗? Andy还好吗?
What's up? Is everything okay? Is Andy okay?
我们很好 别担心 Sebastian在你那里吗?
Yeah. Don't worry about it. Is Sebastian there?
是啊 他在 你想让他接电话吗?
Yeah, he is. Do you want me to get him for you?
不用了
No, no.
不 没事 接着睡觉吧
No, it's okay. Go back to sleep.
早上我再打给你
I'll call you in the morning.
好的 我爱你
Okay. I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
喂 Chris?
Chris?
Chris 我一直打电话你没接 出什么事了?
Chris, I've been trying to call you. What's going on?
Andy带了些货上船
Andy picked something up.
什么? 我们不是不干这个了嘛
Really? I thought we weren't doing that.
没得选择
I didn't have a choice.
这得谢谢Andy先斩后奏啊 是吧?
Thank God for Andy taking the initiative, though, huh?
可惜我不打算带着
Too bad I'm not bringing it in.
事实上我在想直接把毒品扔海里去
I'm thinking of dumping it in the sea, actually.
为什么要这么做?
Why would you do that?
这样我们就都完蛋了!
Then we would all be fucked!
相信我
Take it on faith.
我要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
出什么事了?
Is something wrong?
我说过近期会给你回复的
I told you I would call you with an update.
再拖几天时间我都想
You've got a few more days left
把你头割下来 塞进你屁股里了
before I cut your head off and stick it up your ass.
而你却问我 "出什么事情了?"
And you're asking me, "Is there anything wrong?"
我有批货要进来
Well, I got something coming in.
听起来你没什么底气啊
You don't sound so sure.
我肯定 那批货会来的
I'm sure. It's coming in.
Abney 你不适合干这一行
Flying solo ain't for sidekicks, Abney.
我他妈以前就警告过你
I fucking warned you.
你第一次来找我借钱
When you first came to me for help
维持你这小本生意的时候
in keeping your little business afloat,
我就警告过你
I fucking warned you.
我说 "你得知道什么时候该住手"
I said, "You've got to know your limitations."
"不要贪得无厌!"
"Don't live beyond your fucking means!"
我一般不这么找人要债
I don't normally do this fucking shit.
警告说不按时给钱的后果
Telling you what's going to happen when you don't pay.
这有什么用呢? 你知道规矩 是吧?
What's the fucking point? You know the rules, right?
是的
Right.
你自己小心点 Abeney
You take care, Abney.
杰克威士忌 纯的
Jack, neat.
你不是戒酒了么
Somebody's off the wagon.
我想让你去找Kate
I want you to go see Kate.
我还以为她是你的人呢
Man, I thought she was your family.
要我说 你对他老婆有意思 你就去上
You know, if you want to fuck his wife, you fuck his wife.
但别浪费我时间好让你英雄救美
But don't waste my time so you can play a hero.
Chris现在拿不定主意
Chris is falling apart out there.
他想把毒品扔了
He's going to dump the package.
不准碰她 吓吓她就行了
Don't touch her. Just get her attention.
好吧
All right.
Yeah.
天哪
Oh, man.
你觉得这能蒙混过关?
Do you think it's going to work?
- 可以的  - 你确定?
- It's going to work.  - You think so?
你上过化学课吗? Tarik
Did you take science in school, Tarik?
上过
Yeah.
那你应该知道盐能溶解于水的 傻瓜
Then you should know salt dissolves in water, bitch.
你们要走了吗?
Are you leaving soon?
嗯 Sebastian正在带孩子们过来
Yeah, Sebastian is dropping the boys off.
我们准备回家
We're going home.
没错 Chris要回来了
Oh, that's right. Chris is coming home.
没错
Yeah.
那估计你明天一早上都笑得合不拢嘴了吧?
So, you'll be all smiles in the morning?
希望如此
I hope so.
你走吧 我来搞定
You get out of here, I got it.
晚安
Good night.
- 晚安  - 晚安 宝贝
- Good night.  - Good night, baby.
我把门锁上
I'll lock the door.
谢了
Thanks.
天哪!
Oh. My God!
给我死远点!
Get the fuck away from me!
我朋友马上就来了 他会打得你...
My friend will be here, he'll kick your...
我要说的很简单
I'm going to be perfectly fucking clear.
打电话给你丈夫 叫他别把货扔海里!
You call your husband and you tell him not to dump it in the water!
你告诉他 你 Michael还有Eddie的生死全在他一念之间
You tell him that you, Michael and Eddie are all depending on him.
听清楚了吗?
Do you understand me?
听到没有?
离我孩子远点!
Stay away from my kids!
他有枪!
He's got a gun!
等等! 你在干什么?
Whoa! What are you doing?
没事了
Hey.
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
亲爱的 去我的车上呆着
Honey, I want you to get in the truck with me.
孩子们也在里面 好吗?
The kids are inside, all right?
你身上有酒气
You smell like alcohol.
嗯 我喝了点酒
Yeah, I had a drink.
你喝酒了还要开车带着我的孩子? 你开什么玩笑?
You're driving my kids around drunk? Are you fucking kidding me?
别担心 他和你说什么了?
Relax. What did he say to you?
孩子们 快出来 上我的车 快走
Come on, get out. We're going in my car. Let's go.
Kate! 孩子们 回车上呆着
Kate! Guys, get back in the car.
Kate 你干什么?
Kate, what are you doing?
Kate! Kate! 回我车上去
Kate! Kate! Get in the truck.
该死
Fuck.
他知道孩子们的名字
He knew the kids' names.
别挂 我听不太清楚 等我到外面再说
Hold on, you're breaking up, okay? Let me go outside.
噢 该死
Oh, fuck.
运河上的手机信号太差了 别挂 我往外走
Cell service sucks here on the river. Hold on, I'm going outside.
听到吗? 他让我告诉你...
Hello? He told me to tell you...
等会儿再说 我听不清你说什么
No, hold on. I can't hear you.
他让我告诉你 别把东西丢进...
He told me to tell you not to dump it in...
他让我告诉你 别把东西丢掉
He told me to tell you not to dump it.
谁?
Who did?
还能有谁? 闯进我店子里的混蛋啊!
Who? The asshole who came to the house!
该死 是谁告诉他的?
Who the fuck told him?
你说什么?
What?
孩子们还好吗?
Are the boys okay?
他们很好 我们在Jeanie家
They're here. We're at Jeanie's.
Kate? 听到吗?
Kate? Hello?
Chris 你快回来吧
Chris, please come home.
Chris 听到吗?
Chris?
Chris 你在吗?
嘿 怎么样了?
Hey, how did it go?
我们用木板把玻璃窗封了起来
We boarded up the front window.
警察做了现场记录 他们正在抓捕那家伙
The cops took a report. They're looking for the guy.
好的
All right.
他们想和你谈谈
They want to talk to you.
好 我明天早上就去警局
Yeah. I'm going to go by in the morning.
他们现在就想和你谈谈
They want to talk to you now.
但我们连生活用品都没有 我得去Sebastian家拿一下
But we have no stuff. I've got to go to Sebastian's to get our stuff.
你能帮我带会儿孩子吗?
Would you mind watching the boys for a second?
看看你额头都伤成什么样了
Look at your forehead.
你确定不需要我带你去医院看看?
Are you sure you don't need me to take you to the hospital?
不用 只是... 看上去比较糟而已
No, it's just... it looks worse than it is.
只是有点疼 差不多只是个擦伤 知道吗?
It just hurts. Like a bruise, you know?
我现在就去 免得之后事情缠身 你懂我的意思吗?
I think I should go now before I can't. You know what I mean?
我马上就回来
I'll see you in a little bit.
- 再见 妈妈  - 我爱你
- Goodbye, Mom.  - I love you.
乖乖听话
Be good boys.
Sebastian 你在吗?
Sebastian?
你是不是告诉了Briggs我要丢掉毒品?
Did you tell Briggs I was going to dump it?
不 我没跟任何人说
No. I didn't tell nobody.
别对我撒谎
Don't lie to me.
Chris 我没撒谎 我一个字都没说出去
Chris, I'm not fucking lying to you. I didn't say shit.
那毒品你是从哪儿弄来的?
Where did you get the drugs?
从一个叫Ruben的人那里
From a guy called Ruben.
Sebastian 你在吗?
Sebastian?
嘿
Hey.
嗨 我只是来拿一下东西
Hi. I'm just getting our stuff.
你饿吗? 我帮你做点吃的吧
Are you hungry? Let me make you some food.
不 不用
No, I can't.
- 船今天回不来了  - 我得回去陪着孩子们
- The boat's not coming in.  - I got to get back to the boys.
Chris今晚就会回来
Chris will be back tonight.
不 他回不来 他今晚回不来的
No, he's not. He's not coming home tonight.
我是说 那艘船大概 呃 可能明天才会到
I mean, the boat's not coming in for, like, I don't know, tomorrow.
Chris交待我好好照顾你们
Chris told me that I had to take care of you,
所以我得好好照顾你们
so I'm going to take care of you.
Sebastian 你没听到我的话吗? 我和孩子们会没事的 好吗?
Sebastian, are you not hearing me? We'll be fine, okay?
好的 没事
Yeah, we're fine.
好 很好 没事 这很好
Okay, good. All right. Good.
拥抱一下
Give me a hug.
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
今天可真是漫长
It's been such a big day.
你到底想干什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
没什么 我没想干什么
Nothing. I'm not doing anything.
我只是想给好朋友一个吻啊 你怎么了?
I'm trying to give my friend a fucking kiss. What's your problem?
你怎么了? Kate 别这样
What's your problem? Kate, come on.
听着 我是说 你难道看不出来吗?
Look, I mean, did you even see this?
别说了
Stop it.
Kate 别这样
Kate.
我们俩认识多久了?
How long have we known each other?
知道吗? 把你的手拿开!
You know what? Get your hands off me!
Kate? 别这样!
Kate? Kate!
该死 别跟着我!
Leave me the fuck alone!
Kate 别这样!
Kate!
上帝啊 Kate!
Jesus Christ. Kate!
我只是想和你说说话
I'm trying to have a conversation with you,
而你却像个孩子一样
and you're acting like a fucking child.
那好 那你离这扇门远点
Okay. Good. Why don't you just walk away from the door,
让我回去陪孩子
and let me get out of here.
你真是个不知感恩的孩子 一个不知感恩的捣蛋鬼...
An ungrateful child. A little fucking brat, who's not grateful for...
你是不是想告诉Chris 我是个不可理喻的疯子?
Do you want to talk to Chris about what a fucking bitch I am?
那我现在就打电话给他!
I'm going to fucking call him on the phone right now!
别打电话给Chris
Don't call Chris.
甜心 我爱你 把门打开
Sweetheart, I love you, but open the door.
我要打电话给Chris!
I'm calling Chris!
别再给他添烦恼了!
Don't mess with his head now!
你为什么不去跟他说这些话?
Why don't you fucking tell him?
该死!
Shit!
宝贝儿 对不起 你还好吧?
Honey, I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Kate 你没事吧?
Kate?
Kate 这不好玩 别耍我了
Kate, it's not funny. Stop fucking around.
该死
Fuck.
你会没事的 一定会没事的
You're going to be okay. You're going to be okay.
该死
Shit.
Kate 没事吧?
Kate?
Kate! 醒醒!
Kate! Kate!
喂
Hey.
我知道你干了什么
I know what you did.
我知道Briggs是你的手下
I know Briggs works for you.
你最好离我家人远点 要不然我杀了你
You stay the fuck away from my family, or I'm going to kill you.
听到了吗?
You hear me?
把毒品带回来 一切都会没事的
Just bring in the package. Everything's going to be fine.
我绝不会把毒品带回来的
I'm not bringing in shit.
你一辈子也别想看到这些毒品了
You'll never see that fucking package.
听着 我并不知道...
You know, I didn't know about...
我不敢相信你了 你耍了我
I can't believe you. You fucking played me.
我没耍你
I'm not playing you.
你等着 我会来找你的
I'm coming. I'm coming for you.
好吧
Okay.
我是Camp船长
Captain Camp.
我是Sebastian
Sebastian.
有什么事 Abney?
What do you want, Abney?
Chris Farraday在走私毒品
Chris Farraday is running shit.
知道了
Okay.
他想把毒品丢进运河里
He's going to dump the package.
如果你能拦住他 我就把他的那份钱给你
If you make sure he doesn't, I will give you his share.
天呐 Abney 你真是个冷血的畜生
Jesus, Abney. You are one cold rat bastard.
好吧
All right.
但是如果Farraday不交出毒品的话
But if Farraday don't give it up,
我就把缉毒队的人叫来 你的货也会被没收
I'm going to call in the dogs, and your package is getting seized.
不 他会说的 他不会冒蹲窑子的险
No, he'll tell you where it is. He won't risk doing time.
下次你要再想用我的船走私
Next time you want to run shit on my ship,
你得做得漂亮点 而且给我也分一份红
you do it right and pay a fare like everybody else.
- 东西在哪儿?  - 什么东西?
- Where is it?  - Where's what?
你在走私东西 我知道你在走私东西
You're running something. I know you're running something.
船长先生 我可没在走私
I'm not running anything, Captain.
你想来这套? 给我搜
You want to play that way? Check.
这是你唯一的机会
This is your one chance.
你是想现在交出来 还是想让我叫海关的人来?
You give it up now, or you want me to call CBP?
我没走私东西
I'm not running anything.
你老婆让我帮她带点巴拿马狗粮回家吃
Your wife asked me to bring some Panamanian dog shit home
然后再和她翻云覆雨...
for her to eat and rub in her fucking cunt...
- 去你妈的 你个混蛋  - 但我可没那闲工夫
- Fuck you, you piece of shit.  - But I didn't have time.
你这愚蠢的混蛋! 你真的想这么搞?
You dumb-ass motherfucker! This is how you want it?
没错 我就想跟你对着干
Yeah, this is how I want it.
你想像你愚蠢的老爹一样进监狱吗
You want to go down just like your dumb-ass daddy,
你这该死的蠢货?
you piece of shit mick?
算了
Fuck this.
这次你可玩完了 混蛋
You made it now, motherfucker.
明白吗?
Right?
无论你把东西藏在哪儿 海关的人会找到的
Whatever it is, CBP is going to find it.
没错 他在餐厅里
Yeah, he's in the cafeteria.
你可以行动了
You're clear.
快点 快点
Come on, come on.
该死! 快接电话 伙计
Shit! Pick up the phone, buddy.
这里是新奥尔良港口海关办公室
Customs and Border Protection, Port of New Orleans.
Redmond打来的 二线
It's Redmond, line two.
嘿Redmond
Redmond.
John 你好 我有条好情报
Yeah, John, I've got a good tip.
有人在我的船上走私
Somebody's making a run on my ship.
真的吗?
Really?
好了 各位伙计们 大家听好了
All right, listen up, guys and gals,
我要一个封锁队在20分钟内准备好部署
I want an interdiction team ready for deployment in 20 minutes.
走吧
Let's go.
104号直升机收到 三分钟后到达
Flight 104, copy that. Three minutes to contact.
准备好 待命
Ready. Standing by.
真该死!
Holy shit!
好吧 本来事情进展得挺顺利的
Well, it was good while it lasted.
谁他妈叫来的海关的人?
Who the fuck called the cavalry in?
例行检查!
Inspection, please!
所有船员都出来
All crew. Everybody.
里面有人吗?
Who's in here?
欢迎登船
Welcome aboard.
好了 先生们 坐下
All right, gentlemen, sit down.
到底出什么事了?
What the fuck is going on?
Larry 检查一下天花板
Larry, check the ceiling.
搬下来
Take it down.
哇! 看看这个
Wow! Look at this.
里面什么都没有
There's nothing in there.
里面没东西吗?
There's nothing in there?
该死!
Shit!
就停这儿
That's enough.
一块防水布
A tarp.
一个空的工具箱
Tool box with nothing in it.
你说车里的味道很奇怪 是吧?
You said you thought it smelled funny, right?
没错 船长
Yes, Captain.
也许这车刚被清理过 应该是这样
Maybe it's just been cleaned. That's about it.
可能是在掩盖什么证据 是吧?
Could be covering up something, maybe?
可能是
Could be.
小心台阶
Watch your step.
把地毯清洁器放进后备箱
Just put the carpet cleaner in the trunk.
放好了吗?
You got it?
放在那里就可以了
Just put it right there, that's fine.
该死
Fuck.
噢 该死
Oh, shit.
D7集装箱里的小货车
The van in D-7.
有什么问题吗?
What about it?
我们正在拆卸那辆车
We're taking it apart now.
但你可以直接告诉我们里面有什么 也省得我们麻烦
But you can just save us the trouble, and tell us what's in it.
我很想帮助你
I would love to help you,
但我完全不知道你在说什么
but I don't know what the fuck you're talking about.
你觉得我们很好骗吗?
Do you think we're stupid?
Jib Lakowski是谁?
And who is Jib Lakowski?
这里写得很清楚 他就是小货车的主人
It says right there, he's the guy shipping the van,
也许你们应该找他谈谈
so maybe you should talk to him.
他2004年就死了
He died in 2004.
那我猜他已经不需要这辆小车了 是吧?
Then I guess he's not going to need the van. Huh?
怎么了 大魔术师?
What's up, Houdini?
有什么要给我的吗?
You got something for me?
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
拜托 伙计 给他吧
Come on, man. Just give it to him.
你到底在说什么?
What the fuck are you talking about?
拜托了 伙计!
Come on, man!
好吧 那就算了 和Andy说永别吧
Yeah, I didn't think so. Say goodbye to Andy.
- Chris! 救我!  - 闭上你的臭嘴!
- Chris! Chris!  - Shut the fuck up!
别丢下我 伙计!
Don't fuck me, man!
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
Chris 救我!
Chris!
快跑 Andy!
Run, Andy!
快起来 Briggs
Fuck, Briggs.
开枪打死这个浑球!
Pull the fucking trigger!
要是我死了 你们就拿不到毒品了
You don't get your dope if I'm dead.
那儿
Here.
就是那栋房子
This is it right here.
这栋房子?
Right here?
没错
Yeah.
怎么 你是在让你奶奶帮你贩毒吗?
What, you got your grandma selling cocaine?
这是我朋友的房子
It's my friend's place.
你最好别耍花招
You better not be messing around,
否则我一枪崩了你
I'll put a bullet in your face.
好了 别紧张 快进来
All right, take it easy. Come on.
- 你朋友在家吗?  - 安静
- Is your friend home?  - Quiet.
相信我 吵醒了那家伙不会有好下场
Trust me, you don't want to wake this fucker up.
一号 请报告你的位置
One, state your position, please.
我在211位置
211, responding.
我们接到了一个住宅安全警报 在King大街452号
We have a home security alarm triggered at 452 King Drive.
嘿 你朋友可真有钱 伙计
Hey, you got some rich friends, man.
过来
Come on.
把门关上
Shut that door.
哇! 你这走私技术可真是世界级的啊 伙计
Whoo! That's some world-class smuggling right there, man.
太棒了!
Yeah!
都拿过来了 伙计
We got it now, man.
检查一下
Check this out.
就是这些了 伙计
This is the shit, man.
验下货
Check this out.
好了
Yeah.
噢 这真是实打实的好货
Oh, that's some real booger-sugar right there.
太棒了
Yeah.
货没问题吧?
It's good?
当然 没问题
Yeah, yeah.
那太好了 我得去一下厕所
Great. I'm going to take a piss,
我从船上下来就一直憋到现在
I've been holding it since I got off the boat.
没问题 你去吧
All right, you do that.
这包裹可真难打开 伙计
It doesn't want to come out, man.
他们包得真严实...
They make it stubborn...
你们他妈的是谁?
Who the hell are you?
你们他妈的在我家里干什么?
What the fuck are you doing in my goddamn house?
回去睡觉吧 老家伙
Go back to bed, old man.
该死 条子来了!
Shit, it's Five-O!
快走! 把东西带上 伙计
Get the fuck out! Pack that shit up, man.
一群傻逼
Dumb shit.
Kate在你那吗 Jeanie? 她不接电话
Jeanie, is Kate there? She's not picking up her phone.
孩子们在你那儿吗?
Are the boys with you?
对 孩子都在我这儿 她没多久之前出去了
Yeah, the boys are here. She left a while ago.
她说要去Sebastian家里拿点东西
Said she was going to Sebastian's to get their stuff.
听着 如果她打电话给你 就让她快点给我回电话
Listen, if she calls you, tell her to call me right away.
太他妈搞笑了
Absolutely fucking ridiculous.
我以前从没见过这么蠢的白痴
I've never seen these idiots before in my life.
那边那个受了伤的蠢蛋弄得我沙发上到处都是血
That one dumbshit right there is bleeding all over my couch,
而他们还在分毒品
and they're cutting up their drugs.
Kate 你在吗?
Kate?
Kate 听到吗!
Kate!
Sebastian 开门!
Sebastian!
我要你们从南面开始灌水泥
I want you guys to pour the cement on the south corner first.
我们能从南面开始吗?
Can we start on the south corner first?
车已经在另一边了 不能从南面开始了
We're set up for the other side. No, we can't.
他妈的快从南面开始给我灌
South corner first hurry the hell up.
你们这些家伙已经拖了够多工时了!
You guys have milked this fucking job long enough!
停车!
Hold it!
我们从南面开始倾倒 把车停到那儿去
We're pouring over on the south corner. Take it over there.
发生什么了? 我以为要从另一边开始呢
What the hell's going on here? I thought we were doing the other side.
你为什么让水泥搅拌车换了地方?
Why are you moving the cement truck?
路都被堵住了
You're blocking the fucking trucks.
是你让人来我家捣乱的?
You send guys to my house?
是吗? 我相信你 把老婆和孩子交给你
Huh? I trusted you with my wife and my kids.
我还把你当兄弟对待
And I fucking loved you like a brother.
Kate在哪儿?
Where is Kate?
我说Kate在哪儿?
Where the fuck is Kate?
我再问一遍 Kate在哪儿?
One more fucking time. Where's Kate?
她死了
She's gone.
你没事吧 Seb?
Are you okay, Seb?
这是谁的手机在响?
Whose phone is this?
是谁把手机丢这儿了?
Who left their phone here?
把搅拌机停下来 快点!
Turn that fucking thing off, now!
Chris 怎么了?
Chris?
噢 天呐!
Oh. My God!
快把这东西停下来!
Turn that fucking thing off!
快叫救护车!
Call an ambulance!
噢 该死
Oh, fuck.
快叫救护车!
Call an ambulance!
他妈的快叫救护车啊 快点!
Call a fucking ambulance, now!
喂 这里需要一辆救护车...
Yeah, I need an ambulance...
噢 该死
Oh, shit.
到West Bank运输公司 没错 快点过来
At West Bank Trucking Company. Yeah, right away.
你确定就是这里吗?
Are you sure this is the right place?
没错
Yeah.
这就是Chris把东西丢下船时给我的坐标
These are the coordinates Chris gave me when he dropped it.
我们肯定没来错地方
We're definitely in the right place.
嘿 Chris
Chris.
对不起 真对不起
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
你拿了一点 我赢了
I got that. And you got one.
你出千 是我赢了
You cheated. It's mine.
噢!
Oh!
太棒了!
Yeah!
快看 伙计! 我真不敢相信
Oh, man! I can't believe it.
满满一海面的钱啊!
A sea full of money!
我们得把钱捞起来
We got to get in.
- 把钱捞上船  - 没错
- Get it in here.  - Yeah.
捞上来 小心点 那儿很滑
Pull it in. Be careful, it's slippery right there.
哇!
Whoa!
你没事吧?
Are you all right?
没事 我很好
Yeah, I'm all right.
伙计?
Bud?
106号车
And I have sold it.
以4500美元成交 下一辆
4,500, number 106. Next one.
122号车 300美元起拍
Call lot number 122. Come bid 300.
出价300美元 有人出价400美元
A high of 300, I have to get 400.
400美元 这里有人出价500美元 有人出价550美元吗?
Got 400, got a $500 bid. Five-and-a-half?
有人出价650美元
Five to six-and-a-half.
有人出价700美元 现在价格是750美元
I'm going to seven, going to seven-and-a-half.
有人出价800美元吗? 有吗?
Can I have an $800 bid? Get an 800?
这位77号
And I have sold it.
以750美元拍得此车 谢谢你 先生 下一辆
Seven-and-a-half to number 77. Thank you, sir. Next one.
私人领地 请勿擅入
我给你250万美元买这些货
I'll take it off your hands for 2.5.
没有300万免谈
I'm not taking any less than three.
好吧 300万
Okay, three.
跟我来
Come on.
你去了巴拿马 是吧?
So you were down in Panama, were you?
没错
Yeah.
你有没有听说过杰克逊・波洛克的那幅名画?
Did you hear about that famous painting by Jackson Pollock?
在巴拿马被人抢了
It got ripped off in Panama.
拜托 新闻已经铺天盖地了
Come on, it's been all over the news.
我真不知道
No. No idea.
那东西值多少钱?
What's that thing worth, anyway?
大概值1亿4000万
About 140 million.
那在黑市上呢 能卖到2000万吗?
What's that, 20 on the black market?
至少这个价
At least.
我买错东西了 是吧?
I'm in the wrong business, huh?
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
上车 快上车
Get in, get in.
快点!
Hurry up!
哇!
Whoo!
太棒了!
Wow. Whoo!
2000万
Twenty.
那块布值2000万!
Twenty! It's twenty!
2000万美元
Twenty million.
太棒了!
Yes!
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/==--
协调：心仪Sally 潇妹纸
翻译：死神夜月 夏日尾日记 RK翔 千欲 影子
校对：影子  故故好忙